{
    "subject": "resource/Inukai_Tsuyoshi",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Japan",
    "human_readable": "Inukai Tsuyoshi was born in Japan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9347443580627441,
            "question": "Where was Inukai Tsuyoshi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8899396657943726,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Inukai Tsuyoshi was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723983645439148,
            "question": "What was Inukai Tsuyoshi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7095165848731995,
            "question": "Was Inukai Tsuyoshi born in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6595544219017029,
            "question": "What country is Inukai Tsuyoshi associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5390942692756653,
            "question": "In what era did Inukai Tsuyoshi live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43038710951805115,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Inukai Tsuyoshi's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2965297996997833,
            "question": "Did Inukai Tsuyoshi hold any important positions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17270733416080475,
            "question": "What is Japan famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09435845166444778,
            "question": "Are there any notable figures from Japan you can tell me about?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Inukai Tsuyoshi was born in Japan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_582_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Japan famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_582_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Inukai Tsuyoshi hold any important positions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_582_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Inukai Tsuyoshi's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_582_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_582_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate the triple \"Inukai Tsuyoshi was born in Japan\", we need to check if the documents mention Inukai's birthplace as Japan.\n\nAfter analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_582/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt mentions Inukai Tsuyoshi was born in 1855.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_582/re-ranker-msmarco/51.txt and others mention that Inukai was born to a samurai family of Niwase Domain, which is now part of Okayama city, Okayama Prefecture, in Japan.\n\nThe documents indeed suggest that Inukai Tsuyoshi was born in Japan. Therefore:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Inukai Tsuyoshi was a Japanese politician and cabinet minister, indicating he was born in Japan. While the exact date of birth varies slightly across the provided documents (April 20, 1855, or June 4, 1855), the fact that his place of birth is consistently identified as Bizen Province, which is part of Okayama Prefecture, Japan, supports this statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}